ladies and gentlemen the 45th and final
president of the United
States wow thanks for agreeing to pay
for my border law yeah the whole thing
and three burritos for Life thanks
thanks the president of
Mexico president Mr President Mr
President um Robert Müller has assembled
a grand jury in the Russia probe do you
have any comments unfair I'm supposed to
be Tried by a jury of my peers where are
they going to find 12 presidents who are
allegedly being blackmailed by
Putin why does your immigration plan
play so much importance on the ability
to speak English if you want to live
here you need to talk English very good
as a President Who English great me no
job good is important for job do me
stand with good American like local milk
people so true so true how do you
respond to reports that the White House
is in chaos no there's no chaos and
that's why tonight's theme is
chaos you just said there's no chaos
right that's why tonight's theme is
order I have a new Chief of Staff
General John Kelly a very tough guy and
I trust the general he gets me the best
car insurance rates
online which as we all know saves some
time Kelly has done such incredible work
with deportation this guy tears families
apart and I can't wait to see what he'll
do to mine you want you want him to tear
your family apart what no maybe I don't
know some of them our theme is chaos I
thought it was order you're out of order
I'm the president chaos believe it let's
roll